Guide to the Office of the Registrar, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of the Registrar, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, student records
1903-2007
RU 922
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
125.5
The records consist of transcripts and grade lists for students in Yale College and Sheffield Scientific School maintained by the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences Office of the Registrar.
Yale University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-F (YRG 9-F), Yale College student records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Registrar for the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 2002-2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of transcripts and grade sheets for students in Yale College and Sheffield Scientific School maintained by the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences Office of the Registrar.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Faculty of Arts and Sciences; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School
- Yale College student transcripts, 1925-1967; Accession 2003-A-067
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2043
- Yale College student transcripts, circa 1926-1970; Accession 2003-A-107
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
- Engineering student transcripts, circa 1960-1989; Accession 2003-A-162
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  Scope and Contents
  Transcripts are not in strict alphabetical order.
- Yale College transcripts, 1967; Accession 2005-A-120
- Yale College transcripts, 1967-1978; Accession 2005-A-148
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  Partial inventory only. Contains only double-sided or multiple-paged records.
- Student grade lists, 2004-2007; Accession 2009-A-217
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2083
  - Accounting, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - African Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - African-American Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Applied Math, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Applied Physics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arabic, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Archaeological Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Architecture, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Art, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Astronomy, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Biostatistics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - British Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CBIO, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CDE, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemical Engineering, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chemistry, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Child Study, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chinese, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Classic Civilizations, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cognitive Science, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - College Seminars, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Comparative Lit, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Computer Science, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Czech, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Drama School, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - East Asian Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Economics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Egyptian, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Electrical Engineering, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - English, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Environmental Engineering, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Environmental Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - EMD, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Film Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - French, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Genetics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - GHD, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - German, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - German Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Greek, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Hebrew, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Hindi, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - History, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - History of Art, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - HPA, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Humanities, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Humanities (DS), Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Immunobiology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - International Studies/Internat'l Relations, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Italian, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Japanese, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Korean, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Latin, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Law School, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Linguistics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Literature, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Management, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Math, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - MCDB, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - MBandB, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Modern Greek, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Music, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Music School, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Near East Languages, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - NBIO, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Neuroscience, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Nursing, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Operations Research, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Pathology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Persian, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Philosophy, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Physics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Polish, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Political Science, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Portuguese, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Psychology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Religion, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Religious Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Renaissance Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Russian, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Russian and East European Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Science, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Serbian and Croation, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Sociology, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Southeast Asian Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Spanish, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Special Divisional, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Statistics, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Study of the City, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Teacher Prep, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Theater Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Turkish, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Vietnamese, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Majors, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Dist Req, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Accounting, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - African Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - African-American Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - American Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Applied Math, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Applied Physics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Arabic, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Archaeological Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Architecture, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Art, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Astronomy, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - British Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - CDE, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Chemical Engineering, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Chemistry, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Child Study, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Chinese, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Classic Civilizations, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Cognitive Science, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - College Seminars, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Comparative Lit, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Computer Science, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Czech, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Drama School, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - East Asian Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Economics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Egyptian, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Electrical Engineering, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - English, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Environmental Engineering, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Environmental Health, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Environmental Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Film Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - French, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Genetics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - German, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - German Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Greek, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Hebrew, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Hindi, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - History, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - History of Art, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Humanities, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Immunobiology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Indonesian, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - International Studies/Internat'l Relations, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Italian, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Japanese, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Judaic Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Korean, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Latin, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Latin American Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Law School, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Linguistics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Literature, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Management, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Math, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - MBIO, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - MCDB, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - MBandB, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Modern Greek, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - Music, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - Music School, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - Near East Languages, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - Neuroscience, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - Operations Research, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - Pathology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - Persian, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Pharmacology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Philosophy, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Physics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Polish, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Political Science, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Portuguese, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Psychology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - Religious Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - Renaissance Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - Russian, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - Russian and East European Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - Science, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - Serbian and Croation, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - Sociology, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - Spanish, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - Special Divisional, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - Statistics, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - Study of the City, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - Tamil, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - Teacher Prep, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - Theater Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - Turkish, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - Vietnamese, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Spring 2005 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - Accounting, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 215)
  - African Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 216)
  - African-American Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - American Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - Anthropology, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Arabic, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Architecture, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Art, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Astronomy, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - British Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Chemistry, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Chinese, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Cognitive Science, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Computer Science, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Drama School, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - East Asian Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Economics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - English, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Ethnicity Race and Migration, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Film Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - French, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - German, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - Hebrew, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - History, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - History of Art, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 246)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 247)
  - Humanities, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 248)
  - International Relations, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 249)
  - International Security Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 250)
  - Italian, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 251)
  - Latin American Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 252)
  - Law School, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - Linguistics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 254)
  - Literature, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - Management, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 256)
  - Math, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 257)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 259)
  - MCDB, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  - Music, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - Music School, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  - Philosophy, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  - Physics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  - Political Science, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 265)
  - Psychology, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 266)
  - Russian and East European Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 267)
  - Sociology, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Spanish, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  - Statistics, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  - Theater Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  - Theology, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 272)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Fall 2005 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  - Majors, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  - Dist Req, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  - Accounting, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  - African Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  - African-American Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 278)
  - American Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  - Anthropology, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  - Applied Math, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  - Arabic, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  - Archaeological Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 283)
  - Architecture, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  - Art, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  - Astronomy, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  - British Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  - Chemical Engineering, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  - Chemistry, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  - Chinese, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  - College Seminars, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  - Comparative Lit, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 293)
  - Computer Science, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  - Drama School, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  - Directed Studies (Literature), Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 296)
  - East Asian Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 297)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 298)
  - Economics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 299)
  - Electrical Engineering, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  - English, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 302)
  - Environmental Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 303)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 304)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  - Film Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 306)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 307)
  - French, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 308)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 309)
  - German, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 310)
  - Greek, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 311)
  - HPA (Health Public Administration), Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 312)
  - History, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 313)
  - History of Art, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 314)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 315)
  - Humanities, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 316)
  - International Studies/Internat'l Relations, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 317)
  - Italian, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 318)
  - Japanese, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 319)
  - Korean, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 320)
  - Latin, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 321)
  - Latin American Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 322)
  - Law School, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 323)
  - Linguistics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 324)
  - Literature, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 325)
  - Management, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 326)
  - Math, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 327)
  - MBandB, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 328)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 329)
  - MCDB, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 330)
  - Music, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 331)
  - Operations Research, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 332)
  - Philosophy, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 333)
  - Physics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 334)
  - Political Science, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 335)
  - Psychology, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 336)
  - Religious Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 337)
  - Russian, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 338)
  - Russian and East European Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 339)
  - Sociology, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 340)
  - Spanish, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 341)
  - Statistics, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 342)
  - Teacher Prep, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 343)
  - Theater Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 344)
  - Vietnamese, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 345)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Folder 346)
  - Majors, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 347)
  - Dist Req Class 2007, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  - Accounting, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  - African Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  - African-American Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  - American Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  - Anthropology, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  - Applied Physics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 354)
  - Archaeological Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 355)
  - Architecture, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  - Art, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 357)
  - Astronomy, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 358)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  - Chemistry, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  - Child Study, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  - Chinese, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  - Classic Civilizations, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  - Cognitive Science, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  - College Seminars, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  - Computer Science, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 366)
  - Drama School, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 367)
  - Directed Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 368)
  - East Asian Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 369)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 370)
  - Economics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 371)
  - Electrical Engineering, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - English, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 373)
  - Environmental Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 374)
  - Ethics Politics and Economics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Film Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - French, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Geology and Geophysics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - German, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - German Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - GHD, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Greek, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Hindi, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - History, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - History of Art, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - History of Science, History of Medicine, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Humanities, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - International Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Italian, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Japanese, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Latin, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Law School, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Linguistics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 394)
  - Literature, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 395)
  - Management, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Math, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - MBandB, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 399)
  - MCDB, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 400)
  - Music, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Music School, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Philosophy, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - Physics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Political Science, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Psychology, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Religious Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - Russian, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - Sociology, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Spanish, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Statistics, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Theater Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Women Gender and Sexual Studies, Fall 2006 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Dist Req class 2008, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - Accounting, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - African-American Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - American Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Anthropology, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Applied Math, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Arabic, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Archaeological Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - Architecture, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - Art, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - Astronomy, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Biomedical Engineering, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 425)
  - British Studies, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 426)
  - CDE, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 427)
  - Chemical Engineering, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 428)
  - Chemistry, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 429)
  - Chinese, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 430)
  - Classical Languages and Literatures, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 431)
  - Classic Civilizations, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 432)
  - Cognitive Science, Spring 2007 (Box 4, Folder 433)